…==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==…
更多精彩影视 请访问 http：//cmct.cc
影片压制：小鱼 字幕调校：小鱼 招募Q号：76846146
片名：人皮客栈II
他说早上好 问你手怎么样了？
He say, "Good morning, " and ask, "How is your hand? "
好点了
It's… It's better.
它会怎样？
What's left of it.
抱歉
Sorry.
等你痊愈之后
We would like to speak with you…
我们会和你谈谈
if you feel well enough.
哦 那好吧
Yeah, that's all right.
- 咖啡？- 不 谢谢
- Coffee? - No, thank you.
跟我们说说你提到的那个在斯洛伐克的地方
Tell us about this place you mention, in Slovakia.
那是个…
It's this…
像某种工厂
It's some kind of factory…
那里的人都很有钱
where these people, these very rich people…
他们花钱折磨和残害孩子
they pay to torture and kill kids.
其中大多数是背包路过旅游的人
Mostly backpackers.
他们杀死了我的两个朋友
And they killed two of my friends.
他们把你从客栈带走
They take you from this hostel…
带你来那座工厂
and they bring you to this factory and…
我去那里找乔许
I went there looking for Josh.
他是我的一个朋友 他们把他带去了那里
He was one of my friends and they took him there and
后来他们…
And they…
他们杀了他
They killed him.
太可怕了
It was horrible.
他问你是怎么活下来的
He ask how you survive.
我…
I…
我是逃出来的
I escaped.
他们的头是谁？
Who organize this place?
我不知道 像是某种狩猎俱乐部 他们…
I don't know. It's some kind of hunting club. They…
他们有同样的纹身
They all have the same tattoo.
是一只狗
It's a dog.
一种猎犬
It's a bloodhound dog.
你说的这个纹身很奇怪
Strange that you mention this tattoo.
为什么？
Why?
因为一个死在
Because someone was found dead…
维也纳火车站洗手间里的人
in a train station bathroom in Vienna…
也有和你描述相同的纹身
with this same bloodhound tattoo you describe.
那天车站的监控录像显示
Security tapes from this station show…
他是从一个月台进去的
him entering from a platform…
那个月台正好停着一辆 从斯洛伐克早到的火车
where a train arrive earlier that day from Slovakia.
它正好途径维也纳那一站
It came through the same station in Vienna.
录像里的那个人就是你
You were on that tape.
是这样的纹身吗？
Did his tattoo look something like this?
这是他妈的怎么了？
What the fuck's going on?
救命啊 快来人啊
Help! Somebody help me!
天呐！
Jesus.
你饿了？
You hungry?
现在是凌晨三点十五分
It's 3:15 in the morning.
这些我不得不和食物一起吃下去
I have to take these with food.
我想知道你是不是也想吃点东西
I wanna know if you want anything.
是的 我想让你跟别人谈谈
Yeah, I want you to talk to someone.
你打算什么时候告诉乔许的妈妈 发生了什么事？
When are you gonna tell Josh's mother what happened?
我不会告诉她
I'm not.
她一直认为她的儿子还在欧洲
She still thinks her sors in Europe.
那我到底要怎么跟她解释？
What the fuck am I supposed to tell her?
她可以直接去报警
She'll go straight to the police.
是啊 没错 是该有人去
Yeah, exactly. Someone should.
不 谁也别去 你不明白的
No, no one should. You don't get it.
这些人对每个人都感兴趣
These people are tied into everyone.
一开始他们只是问问题
Somebody starts asking questions…
然后就会跟着你 直到找到你的住处
they're gonna come after me and find me.
来我祖母的房子？
At my grandmother's house?
虽然我还是个孩子的时候就在这里了
I've been coming here since I was a kid.
但还是很容易迷路
I can barely find the place.
我每次必须问我姐姐
I had to ask my sister for directions.
- 你告诉你姐姐我们在这里？- 是的 怎么了？
- You told your sister we were here? - Yeah. So?
- 还有谁知道？- 没了！
- Well, who else knows? - No one!
天！
Jesus.
我这么做也是为了保护你
I'm doing this for your protection too.
你知道的 不是吗？
You know that, right?
哦 派斯顿
Oh, Paxton…
听着
Look.
我带你回来 是因为我也不好受
I took you back because I felt bad.
但是你快疯了
But you're going crazy.
你每夜都尖叫着惊醒
You wake up every night screaming,
这样我没法睡觉
and I can't sleep.
好吧 以后不会再有了
Well, that won't be a problem anymore.
派斯顿 我不是故意
Paxton, that's not what I…
哦 该死
Oh, fuck.
早上好！
Morning!
派斯顿？
Paxton?
嗨
Hey.
罗娜？
Lorna?
对不起 我在试图进入状态
Sorry. I was trying to be in the moment.
融入其中
Absorb.
你觉得她以前见过阴茎吗？
Do you think she ever saw a cock before this class?
如果她看过 肯定是在波提切利的画里
If she did, it was in a Botticelli.
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
如果我听她再说
If I hear her talk about…
如果我听她再说 波提切利是多么地充满感情
how emotional the Botticelllis are one more time…
我发誓 我会掐死她
I swear to God, I'm gonna choke the bitch to death.
下一次是下周二
Until Tuesday.
去布拉格的行装收拾得怎么样了？
Are you all packed for Prague?
- 牛仔裤 平跟鞋 - 不错
- Jeans. No heels. - Awesome.
我在鹅卵石上做不来的
I can't do it on the cobblestone.
我不知道你怎么办到的
I don't know how you do it.
我能教你 如果你带双高跟鞋的话
I can teach you if you bring heels.
艾希尔
Axelle.
拿起你们的铅笔 小伙子们
Hands on your pencils, boys.
- 他会不会？- 抱歉 姑娘们
- Would he ever? - Excuse me, girls.
- 抱歉 嗨 - 嗨
- Excuse me. Hi. - Hi.
- 我能看看吗？- 哦 画得不太好
- May I see? - Oh, they're just rough.
给她看吧 别害羞
Show her. Don't be shy.
这张画的是你
That's the one of you.
- 哦 太美了 - 谢谢
- Oh, wow, that's beautiful. - Thanks.
你打算多少钱卖？
How much would you want for it?
我不会卖的 这张送你了
I wouldn't sell them. You can have this one.
- 真的吗？- 是的
- Really? - Yeah.
哦 天 太感谢了
Oh, my God, thank you so much.
别客气
You're welcome.
我能请你喝点什么吗？
Can I buy you a drink or something?
哦 实际上我有点迟到了
Oh, I'm actually late.
我们要赶去布拉格的火车 所以
We're catching a train to Prague, but…
- 我不知道 也许下次吧 - 好的
- I don't know. Maybe some other time. - Okay.
- 当然 - 好
- Yeah! Okay. - Okay.
- 回见 - 好的 再见 谢谢
- I'll see you. - All right. Bye. Thanks.
不 爸 是布拉格 我们会没事的
No, Dad. It's Prague. We're gonna be fine.
不是乌克兰
It's not the Ukraine.
不
No.
不 爸 不用订四季酒店
No, Dad, do not book the Four Seasons.
订吧 姐们 订吧 求你了！
Book it, bitch. Book it. Please!
哪里有大学生
Because, Dad, no college students…
住四季酒店的？
are staying at the Four Seasons.
你知道的 那里适合老人
And, you know, it's for old people.
谢谢 不用了
So thank you, but please don't.
什么？
What?
是 我有女伴
Yeah. Yes, we have chaperones.
好的 爱你 再见
Okay, love you. Bye.
天 我讨厌他每隔5分钟
Jesus, I hate that he calls…
就来一个该死的电话
every fucking five minutes.
好了 我们走吧
All right, let's go.
等等 我们还得等个人
Hold on. We gotta wait for someone.
谁？
Who?
- 是的 - 不
- Yeah. - No.
她在宿舍里堵着我
She cornered me in the apartment.
哭着说想家
She's homesick, crying.
那种感觉太糟了 我能说什么呢？
I felt bad. What am I supposed to say?
她想巴尔的摩了？
She's homesick for Baltimore?
我们现在在罗马 拜托
We're in Rome, for fuck's sake.
她没那么差
She's not that bad.
噢 那是新的日记本吗？
Wow, is that a new journal you got there?
是的 准备写旅游日记
Yeah. It's a travel journal.
为了浪漫的回忆
For emotional callbacks.
当然了
Of course.
罗娜 我们要去喝一杯 你来吗？
Lorna, we're gonna grab a drink. You wanna go?
我不去了 谢谢
I'm okay. Thank you.
好吧 一会儿见
All right. Well, we'll see you in a little bit.
加油吧
Knock yourself out, buddy.
一会儿见
See you later.
也不说句对不起 混蛋
Excuse you. Asshole.
她就像一位20岁的老太太
She's like a 20-year-old grandmother.
无论怎样 她会帮我们看东西 她好像也挺开心的
Whatever. She'll watch our stuff. She's happy there.
那是她想做的
That's what she likes to do.
哦 我们没要这些
Oh, we didn't order these.
是那个女孩请你们的
They're from girl.
哇噢 你女友在跟踪我们
Whoa, your girlfriend's stalking us.
嘿 你在这里干嘛？
Hey. What are you doing?
你让我有了旅游的冲动
You inspired me to take a trip.
看这边
Watch this.
你没开玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me.
你好 你叫什么名字？
Hello. What's your name?
你知道哪能找到一些让人兴奋的东西吗？
Do you know where we could score,
比如什么药物之类的
like, party favors?
你想要什么？
What do you need?
我不知道 像大麻或摇头丸之类的 或者是
I don't know. Like, bud and ecstasy and, like…
天使粉？
PCP?
冰毒？皮约特？脱氧麻黄碱？
Ice? Peyote? Crank?
好 那就大麻和摇头丸好了
Okay, okay, bud and X are good.
好的
Sure.
一起来我的车厢 我有
We go back to my car. I got some.
怎么样？
Yeah?
- 好吗？- 好的
- Yeah? - Okay.
该死 你知道吗？
Fuck. You know what?
我记得有的 但现在找不到了
I'm trying but I can't find them.
稍等一下 好吗？
Just hang on, yeah?
- 你们想喝点什么吗？- 不用了
- You want drink? - No, I'm fine.
嘿 没关系的
Hey, you know what?
不用找了 我们到了布拉格
It's okay because we can just get it…
也能在那边的俱乐部里弄到的
at the club when we go to Prague.
不 等等
No, stay.
我会找到的 明白吗？
I find them. Okay?
你身上的味道不错
You smell nice.
我们得走了 罗娜还在等我们呢
Whit, we gotta go. Lorna's waiting.
是的 我们还有个朋友
Yeah, we have our friend.
- 你们还有个朋友？- 是的
- You have friend? - Yeah.
一 二 三 正好三对三
One, two, three, perfetto.
要不然 我们还得轮着上 对吧？
Otherwise, we have to take turns, huh?
我们得走了 别介意
You know, we're gonna go, so never mind.
去哪？
Where you go?
我就知道你们在耍我 你们这群骚货
I knew you were a tease, you fucking cunt.
你刚才叫我什么？
What the fuck did you call me?
我叫你愚蠢欠干的美国骚货
I called you stupid fucking American cunt!
- 去你妈的！- 你知道什么
- Fuck you! - You know what?
到布拉格还有很长的距离 你这个婊子
The train to fucking Prague is long, you bitch.
我们会去找你的
We'll come see you.
你疯了吗？
Are you fucking insane?
什么？我非常讨厌那句话
What? I fucking hate that word.
「噢 愚蠢欠干的美国骚货」
"Oh, you stupid American cunt."
气坏我了
I fucking lost my temper.
好了 但这里不是学校
Okay, but it's not like we're on campus and you…
你能给院长打电话 写个报告什么的
can call the dean and file a report or something.
哦 我的天 罗娜 发生什么了？
Oh, my God. Lorna, what happened?
有个人拿走了我的iPod
Some guy took my iPod.
什么？
What?
车上有没有
Is there, like, a police officer…
警察之类的？
on the train or something?
- 我去看看 - 好的
- Yeah. I'll go check. - Okay.
我把所有东西都存在里面了
It had everything.
太可怕了 我很抱歉
That's awful. I'm so sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
给你
Here you go.
那些讨厌的家伙来了
It's those fucking guys.
是那些混蛋意大利人
The fucking guys,
就是走廊尽头房间的那几个
the Italian guys from the room down the hall.
- 我们怎么办？- 保持安静
- What do we do? - Just be quiet.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
打扰了 你们中有谁丢了这个吗？
Excuse me. Did one of you girls lose this?
噢 上帝！
Oh, my God!
你怎么知道这是我的？
How did you know this was mine?
我看见一个人从你房间里跑出来
I saw some guy run out of your room.
他打算抢我的包
He tried to take my bag.
我把他打倒了 这个是从他口袋里掉出来的
I fought him off and this felled out of his pocket.
我有点担心
I'm a little worried he might…
他会回来找我
come back looking for me.
你想过来和我们一起住吗？
Do you wanna come in here and hang out with us?
- 真的可以吗？- 是的 这里还有一个空位
- Really? - Yeah, we have an extra seat.
- 是的 来吧 - 真的
- Yeah, come in. - Totally.
谢谢
Thank you.
我想
I think…
我们需要来点这个
we all need a little of this.
哦 太棒了
Oh, awesome.
哦 不 谢谢 我不喝酒
Oh, no, thanks. I don't drink.
谢谢
Thank you.
我爸爸总是说
As my father always says:
「为你的健康干杯！」
"Nazdrovia." To your health.
你们是去到布拉格看球赛吗？
So are you going to Prague for the football match?
我有点想家了
I kind of wanna go home.
不是我说你们
Oh, I don't blame you.
曾经我也在过夜的火车上被劫过两次
I got robbed twice on the overnight train.
欧洲没有什么真正安全的地方
There are so few safe places left in Europe.
你要去哪里？
So where are you going?
只是一个小小的温泉度假旅行而已
On a little spa vacation.
在哪？
Where?
斯洛伐克
Slovakia.
等等 那里不是好像在打仗吗？
Wait, wasrt there, like, some war in Slovakia?
斯洛伐克已经50年没有过战争了
There hasn't been war in Slovakia for 50 years.
你说的是波斯尼亚 亲爱的
That's Bosnia, darling.
- 哦 就你知道 - 的确是这样
- Oh, like you knew. - I did so.
那里的温泉怎么样？
What are the spas like there?
那里有世界上最好的自然温泉
They're the best natural hot springs in the world.
我每年都会去两次
I go twice a year.
那里不会有意大利人找你麻烦
It's great to get away from the Italian guys.
因为那是不可能的
They get to be a bit much.
哇噢 真的是温泉？
Wow, hot springs?
听上去很有保健作用 我想去那
That sounds so therapeutic. I wanna go.
那简单
It's very easy.
你们只需在布拉格转车就行了
You just have to switch trains in Prague.
那一定非常好
It could be nice.
这周末我已经受够了那些下流混蛋
You know? I had enough gross guys for one weekend.
好吧 我们去
Okay, we'll go.
你知道住哪里好吗？
Do you know of a good place to stay?
穿鞋走会容易得多
Smart move with the shoes.
什么？这很简单 我一定要试试
What? It's so easy. You have to try it.
嗨 我能为您效劳吗？
Hi. Can I help you?
我的朋友们需要一个房间
I need a room for my friends, please.
好的 没问题
Yeah, cool.
请出示你们的护照
Your passports, please.
美国人 非常好
American. Good.
不错 每晚10欧元
Yeah, cool. It's 10 Euros for night.
不 我来
No. I got this one.
不 这次轮到我了
No. It's on me.
- 谢谢 - 给你钱
- Thank you. - Money.
谢谢
Thanks.
这是你们的钥匙
Here are your keys.
这是今晚
And this is a notice for the…
丰收节晚会的公告
harvest fair tonight, girls.
肯定很好玩
Will be sexy good times. Come on.
他们管它叫多极克 我知道 每年都会有的
It's Dozinky. I know that. They have it every year.
- 是的 - 很多音乐 舞蹈 奇装异服
- Yeah. - Lots of music, dancing, costumes.
哦 天 我们能去吗？
Oh, my gosh! Could we go?
- 听上去像某种同性恋聚会 - 抱歉
- It sounds kind of gay. - Excuse me.
哦 我们一定要去
Oh, we are so going to the harvest festival.
- 来吧 这边 - 谢谢
- Come on. This way. - Thank you.
不用客气
You're welcome.
你觉得这里的房间会有壁画吗？
Do you think they have any frescoes in the room?
「闲人免进」
这房间看上去有一段历史了
Wow, this room feels so timeless.
你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding right now?
哦 天
Oh, my God!
太性感了
Sexy.
来嘛
Come here.
太棒了！
Yes! Yes!
Yeah!
我就是这个意思 嗯？
That's what I'm talking about, huh?
「竞拍结束」
托德 怎么了？
Todd, what's up?
没事 我们刚吃完早饭
Yeah, nothing. We're just finishing up breakfast.
真的？
Really?
我不敢相信
Wow, I didn't think…
天啊 你确定要这么做？
Jesus. You sure?
是的 没问题 我现在就能走
Yeah, yeah, okay. I can go right now.
我会告诉她得去见一个客户
I'll tell her I have to meet a client.
好的
Okay.
一会儿见
See you.
天 这个镇子太迷人了
Gosh! This village is so enchanting.
罗娜 你现在是不是非常有写日记的冲动？
Lorna, are you having a "journal-gasm" right now?
确实是 想写很多
Actually, yes. Multiple ones.
我要写这个镇子有多美
I get to write about how beautiful this village is
我还要写你是多么讨厌
and I get to write about what a raving bitch you are.
她敢反驳了
She comes back swinging!
- 就要这样 - 谢谢
- Well-played. - Thank you.
美元！
Dollar!
你们有一美元吗？
Do you guys have a dollar?
- 我有 - 哦 不 不 不
- I got it. - Oh, no, no, no.
不 我有 让我来
No, no, no. I got it. I got it. Let me.
我有薄荷糖
I have Smints.
来块薄荷糖怎么样？
Would you like a Smint?
婊子！
Bitches!
欢迎来到斯洛伐克
Welcome to Slovakia.
你们俩都是拐角的套房 可以看到整条河的景色
You both have corner suites with views of the river.
这是你们的呼叫器
Here are your pagers.
非常好 谢谢
Perfect. Thank you.
- 你准备好了吗？- 是的 准备好了
- You ready to do this? - Yeah, I'm ready.
真的？
Really?
但你看上去垂头丧气的样子
Because you look like your dog just died.
我只是时差没倒过来
I'm just jet-lagged, man.
冲个澡就会没事了
I'll take a shower and I'll feel better.
- 好吧 - 谢谢
- All right. - Thanks.
哦 天
Oh, my God!
嗨 姐妹们
Hey, guys!
怎么了？
Yes?
买些装饰一下房间
For the apartment.
好主意
Awesome, dude.
那些剑看起来要1000欧元
Those swords are like 1000 Euros.
相信我 她能负担得起
Trust me, she can afford it.
她有很多零花钱吗？
Does she get, like, a really big allowance?
不 说是一大笔遗产更确切
No, it's more like an ineritance.
她妈妈在她12岁时就去世了
Her mom died when she was 12,
所有的东西都留给了她
and like, left her everything.
所以是她给她爸爸零花钱
And so she keeps her dad on an allowance.
- 真的？- 是的
- Really? - Yeah.
如果她愿意的话 差不多整个斯洛伐克都可以买下来
She could pretty much buy Slovakia if she wanted to.
相当酷 不是吗？
Yeah. It's pretty rad.
好
Yeah!
坏小子
Badass.
让我看看这个婊子
Let me see this motherfucker.
该你了 兄弟
You're up, bro.
我想我就跳过纹身好了
I think I'm gonna pass on the tattoo.
来吧 坐下
Come on, man, sit down.
纹身不适合我 不是我的风格
A tattoo's not really me. It's not my style.
我不知道 我天生不喜欢针
I didn't know and I don't like needles.
非常不喜欢
I don't like needles very much.
伙计 你说什么呢 来坐下
Dude, what are you doing? Sit down.
这会有麻烦的
Here's the problem.
琳达看见后 我该怎么解释？
Linda. What is she gonna say when she sees this?
我的妻子是理解不了的
My wife is not gonna really understand.
有什么别的选择吗？
Is there some other option?
每个人都得纹身 合同里说明了的
Everyone must get tattooed. Part of contract.
是的
Yeah.
就这么办吧 来吧 老兄
Let's do it. Come on, man.
为什么就不能坐下呢？这些家伙可不是在玩游戏
Why don't you sit down? These guys aren't playing.
纹身真的很难解释清楚 托德
A tattoo is a little difficult to explain, Todd.
你好像没有什么问题解释不了的
Didrt seem like you had any problem explaining…
上次你从泰国带回去的淋病
the gonorrhea you brought back from Thailand.
你怎么每次都提到那个淋病
Can't believe you're bringing up the gonorrhea…
有什么问题吗？
Is there any problem here?
不 我只是不知道这是合同的一部分
No, no. I just didn't know that this was part of it.
斯图亚特
Stuart.
这可不是像去妓院
This is not like going to a whorehouse.
你不能在中途退出
You can't just back out.
坐到那该死的椅子上去
Get in the fucking chair.
好样的
Yeah.
没事的 老兄 看看这个
Come on, man. Look at this.
我非常引以为豪
I'm fucking proud of mine.
看我发现了什么！
Look what I found!
在你们评论前
Okay, and before you say anything,
我先说这只是苹果汁 不含酒精的
it's cider, it's non-alcoholic…
是那边的小家伙们弄的
and those little kids right there made it.
- 噢 天 真的吗？- 没错
- Oh, my gosh, really? - Yeah.
- 我要去谢谢他们 - 好吧
- I'm gonna go say thank you. - Okay.
他们不太懂英语
They don't speak much English.
这可能是我尝过的
This is quite possibly…
酒精浓度最高的苹果汁了
the most alcoholic cider I've ever tasted.
好了 这是为她好 她需要锻炼一下
Come on, it's good for her. She needs it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
来 干杯
Well, cheers.
噢 我喜欢的歌 快走
Oh, my God, my song! Let's go!
走吧
Come!
来吧 帅哥 看看你跳得怎么样
Come on, Borat. Let's see what you got.
他们在那
There they are.
三点钟方向
Three o'clock.
- 天 - 是吧？
- Jesus. - Right?
真他妈疯狂 不是吗？临死前最后的表演
It's fucking crazy, huh? Dead ringer.
生日快乐 老兄
Happy fucking birthday, bro.
- 老兄 你去哪？- 找个能看清楚的地方
- Dude, where you going? - In for a better look.
我？
Me?
嗨
Hi.
想和我跳支舞吗？
Would you like to dance with me?
不 谢谢
No, thank you. I'm…
我喝得还不够多
I'm not nearly drunk enough.
来吧 我教你怎么跳
Come on. I'll show you how.
不 真的 很简单的
No, really. It's easy.
不 谢谢 我真的累了 我的脚已经不听使唤了
No. Thank you, really, but my feet. I'm tired.
我本来能帮助你的
I could have helped you.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
嗨
Hey.
那家伙给你找麻烦了？
That guy make you some troubles?
不 他很好
No. He's fine.
他跟你说了什么？
What he say to you?
没什么 他就想和我跳舞
Nothing. He just wanted to dance.
他不会再给你找麻烦了
He won't bother you anymore.
他没有给我添麻烦
Oh, he wasrt bothering me.
来 喝一杯
Here. Take a drink.
- 谢谢 - 别客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
- 噢 对不起 - 别介意
- Oh, I'm so sorry! - Don't worry about it.
太对不起了 我真蠢
I'm so, so sorry. I'm such an idiot.
不 没关系的
No, it's all right.
我得请你一杯
Here, let me get you a drink.
不 不必了
No, you don't need to.
- 不 我一定要 - 不 不
- No, I insist. - No, no.
一定要
I insist.
贝思！贝思！
Beth! Beth!
贝思！我的天
Beth! Oh, my God,
罗曼说想和我一起去坐船
Roman wants to take me on a boat ride…
他是那么的彬彬有礼 那么的迷人
and he's just so suave and he's amazing…
虽然他不会说英语
and he doesn't speak English,
但我们沟通起来却没有任何问题
but we understand each other.
好吧 只要答应我
Yeah. Just promise me you won't go on…
别和他去坐船好吗？
a boat ride with him, okay?
为什么不行？
Why not?
有什么关系？你不喜欢他？
What's the big deal? You don't fancy him?
就是因为他长得
Just because he's not "Whitney approved"…
不是你们喜欢的类型？
or "Beth approved" looking?
不 我根本没这么说过
No, I'm not saying that at all.
我只是想你待在安全的地方
I just want you to stay here where it's safe…
我们要在一起 不要分开行动
we're all together, we don't get separated.
答应我
Just promise me you won't…
别和他去划船
go on a boat ride with him.
罗娜 答应我
Lorna, promise me you won't…
你不会和他去划船
go on a boat ride with him.
贝思 好吧
Beth. It's okay.
- 好 你答应了？- 好的 好的
- Okay. You promise? - Okay, okay, okay.
好
Okay.
罗曼
Roman.
两杯 谢谢
Okay, two, please.
这是你的 非常抱歉
Here you go. I'm so sorry about that.
没关系的
It's okay.
- 干杯 - 谢谢 干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers. Thanks.
你怎么会想到来到这个地方？
So, what brings you to this corner of the world?
她 她挑的头
Her. Firestarter.
那么你呢？
And you?
说实话 我也不知道
I honestly don't know.
抱歉 这里可能
I'm sorry, there's probably…
有一伙斯洛伐克小孩跟你捣蛋
a small army of Slovak boys all fighting over you.
为什么大老远来这里
Why travel all this way just to talk…
只是和一个丑陋的美国人聊天呢
with an ugly American?
你并不丑
You're not that ugly.
是吗？
Really?
好 为这个干杯
Well, cheers to that.
干杯
Cheers.
你朋友看上去玩得相当开心
Hey, your friend looks like she's having fun.
没错
Yeah.
我马上就会听到他们做爱的声音
I get to listen to them have sex later.
我们能换个地方吗？我住在帝温扎克宾馆
Can we switch? I'm over at the Dvorzak hotel and…
可能有三个世纪
it's probably been three centuries…
没有人在那里做过爱了
since anybody's had sex over there.
也许你的桌子已经准备好了
Oh, maybe your table's ready.
这个说来话长了
That's… That's a long story.
好吧 我只能下次再听你说了
Well, I'll have to hear about it another time.
我得走了 这是个小镇子
I'm gonna take off, but it's a small village…
- 我们肯定会再见面的 - 肯定会的
- I'm sure we'll meet again. - I'm sure we will.
好吧 晚安
All right. Good night.
晚安 贝思
Good night, Beth.
我告诉过你我的名字吗？
Did I tell you my name?
不 我是听你朋友这么叫你的
No, no. I heard your friend use it.
但是我忘记介绍自己了 我叫斯图亚特
But I forgot to tell you mine. I'm Stuart.
很高兴认识你 斯图亚特
Good to meet you, Stuart.
晚安
Good night.
罗娜！
Lorna!
罗娜
Lorna.
让一下
Excuse me.
罗娜！
Lorna!
贝思 对不起
Beth, I'm sorry!
你答应过我的
You promised.
我知道
I know.
对不起
I'm sorry!
这里太清静了
It's so peaceful.
太隐蔽了
It's so secluded.
罗曼 你要干吗？
Roman, what are you doing?
过来
Come to me.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
罗曼！罗曼！
Roman! Roman!
刚才在一条船上…现在我也不知道她去哪了
On a boat and I have no idea where she is.
她怎么从那回来？
How does she get back from that?
贝思 好了
Beth, come on!
哦 该死
Oh, fuck!
贝思！
Beth!
我不能让她一个人和这个家伙待在一起
I cannot leave her alone with this guy.
你去吧
You know, you just go ahead…
我来等罗娜
and I'll wait for Lorna.
- 你走吧 没事的 - 好吧
- You go. Yeah. - Yeah?
- 好吧 非常感谢 - 好的
- All right. Thank you so much. - Okay.
- 没问题 - 谢谢
- Sure. Yeah. - Thank you.
该死！
Fuck!
- 你要来吗？- 你还好吧？
- Dude, are you coming? - Are you okay?
我很好 我没事
I'm good. I'm good. No, I'm fine.
- 你还好吧 - 我没事
- Are you all right? - Dude, I'm fine.
再来杯鸡尾酒
Have another cocktail.
好的 晚安
All right, good night.
不 等等 我们要去睡了
No, Whit. We're going to sleep.
- 我们俩？- 是的
- We are? - Yeah.
他很棒吧 是不是很像东方人？
Okay, is he hot, or is he too, like, eastern bloc?
他很好
He's fine.
但是我们现在能不能去休息了？来吧
But can we please go get some rest? Come on.
哦 你太体贴了 但我没事的
Oh, you're so sweet. No, I'm fine.
没问题 我会照顾好她的
It's okay. I'll take care of her.
我相信你会的 但今晚不行 好吗？
I'm sure you will, but not tonight, all right?
晚安 米洛斯拉夫
Good night, Miroslav.
Good night, Miroslav!
对不起 他刚才太阴沉了
I'm sorry. He was just so shady.
不管怎样 我想干他 不过
Whatever. I wanted to fuck him, but…
我知道你会的 我会补偿你的
I know you did. I'll make it up to you.
我猜今晚又得让
I guess Mr. Rabbit's gonna have to…
「兔子先生」（自慰器）出马了
go down the hole again tonight.
你还有5号电池吗？
Do you have a AA?
兔子先生！
Mr. Rabbit!
到这来 兔子先生
Come here, Rabbit!
你还记得高中第一个
Do you remember the first guy…
跟别人上床的家伙是谁吗？
in your high school to get laid?
不 但我记得最后一个
No, but I remember the last.
嗯 我也记得 小孩格雷格
Well, I do. This kid Greg.
他过完暑假回来
He came back from summer break,
他就变了
something about him had changed.
不是说他的言行举止
It wasrt anything he said or did,
但就感觉有些东西不一样了 你明白的
but something was different. You knew it.
我明白你的意思 就像…
I know what you mean. It's like…
动物那种本能的直觉
you can sense it the way an animal senses it.
没错 就像动物一样
Exactly. Like an animal.
有时你遇见一个人
Sometimes you meet a guy and…
他身上有种让人害怕的东西
there's something fucking scary about him…
这些会让你感觉到
something that makes you think,
这个人曾经杀过人
"This guy has killed somebody."
他不必表现得很强硬
He doesn't have to act tough.
更不用去告诉别人什么
He never has to say it.
但就像动物一样 你能感觉到
But like an animal, you can sense it.
这种家伙能做
You know that this guy's got the balls…
别人不敢做的事情
to do what few others can.
今天过后你也会这样 我的朋友
And that's you after today, my friend.
人们会畏惧你
People are gonna fucking fear you.
琳达也会害怕你
Linda is gonna fucking fear you.
今天你我要做的事情
What we do today is gonna pay off…
会在今后一生中得到回报
every day for the rest of our lives.
- 你的呼叫器呢？- 放在房间里了
- Where's your pager? - It's back in the room.
你怎么搞的
Come on. What the fuck?
我想你会带上的
I just figured you had yours.
是吗？可我觉得
Is it me? Because it feels like you're,
你一直在犹豫什么
like, having second thoughts.
你的心思从来就没放在上面
You've never really been into this.
我感觉是我硬把你拉进来似的
I feel like I'm talking you into it.
我不想这么做
I don't wanna be doing something…
也不想一直讨论这个问题
and keep talking about it…
这和想象得有点不同
It's different from taking on an image.
我他妈已经厌倦一直谈论这个了
I am so fucking tired of talking about it.
现在我们就要这么做
It's time we fucking do it.
为了下一阶段
To the next level.
为了下一阶段 不 等一下
To the next level. No, wait.
不是说用白水干杯会倒霉吗？
Isn't it bad luck to toast with water?
没错 今天遇到我们的人都会倒霉
Yeah. Bad luck for whoever meets us today.
是的 开始游戏吧
Yeah. Let the games begin.
再用力点 再用力点
Hard, hard, hard.
嗨
Hey.
- 嗨 她打过电话吗？- 不 我刚查了
- Hey, did she call? - No. I just checked.
我想罗娜是昨天晚上
I love that Lorna's the only one of us…
我们当中唯一有所收获的人
that got any action last night.
- 嗨 我努力了 - 继续努力
- Hey, I tried. - Keep trying.
是啊 她说过这个地方太宏伟了
Yeah, she'd say this place is majestic.
没错
Sure.
我敢打赌她正在为那个人做早餐呢
I bet she's making him breakfast right now.
不 我猜她正爽得欢呢
No, I bet she's in a cum coma.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
至少她的日记上
At least she has something…
有东西写了
to write about in her journal.
求求你！求求你！
Please! Please!
求求你 停手
Please! Stop!
不！
No!
停手吧！求你了！
Stop! Please! Please!
求你了！求你了！
Please! Please!
求你了 不！
Please, no!
放松
Relax.
过来
Come up here.
惠特尼？
Whit?
艾希尔？
Axelle?
该死
Fuck.
惠特尼！
Whit!
人呢？
Guys!
艾希尔！惠特尼！
Axelle! Whit!
停车 请帮帮我！
Stop. Please help me!
- 走开 - 求你帮帮我
- Go away. - Please help me!
- 给我走开 - 不 不
- Just go away from me! - No, no, no.
救救我 那些人在追我 求你了
Help me. These men are chasing me. Please.
我本来试图帮你 但是你没有听 现在走开！
I tried to help, but you don't listen. Go away!
美元 婊子！
Dollar, bitch!
别打了！
Stop!
进车里
Get in.
好
Yeah.
警察马上就来了
The police will be here soon.
他们在找你的朋友
They are looking for your friends.
谢谢
Thank… Thank you.
再来点茶吗？
More tea?
好的
Please.
谢谢
Thank you.
那么 你和沙夏
So, you and Sasha…
- 你们两个是…？- 噢 不 不
- are you two…? - Oh, no. God, no.
他的年纪可以做我爸爸了
He's old enough to be my dad.
他是做什么的？
What does he do?
他是做拍卖的
He does auctions.
来 我给你拿几件衣服
Come. Let's get you some clothes.
不要！
No!
救命啊！不要！
Help! No! No!
我做错了什么？
What did I do wrong?
请别伤害我 不要伤害我 对不起
Please don't hurt me. I'm sorry.
请别伤害我 请别伤害我
Please don't hurt me. Please don't hurt me.
我不会伤害你
I not hurt you.
没事的 没事
Okay. It's okay.
我给你打扮一下
I clean you up.
请帮帮我
Please, please help me.
你脸上有块擦伤
You have a bruise.
什么东西？
What is that?
你在干吗？
What are you doing?
我要把你打扮得漂漂亮亮的
I make you pretty.
为什么要打扮漂亮？
Pretty for what?
为了客人啊
For the client.
客人？什么客人？
Client? What client?
伸出手来
Give me. No.
不
No.
我们来
We do…
修指甲
nails.
不！
No!
不！不！
No! No!
我的天
Oh, my God.
不！
No!
我有点担心惠特尼
I'm worried about Whit.
惠特尼看上去是个厉害的女孩
Whitney seems like a tough girl.
她会没事的
She'll be okay.
你有块擦伤
You have a scratch.
是的
Yeah.
- 很疼 - 对不起
- It's sore. - I'm sorry.
你的皮肤真美
You have such beautiful skin.
谢谢
Thank you.
他们是谁？
Who's that?
只是一些朋友
Just some friends.
来 你该躺下休息一下了
Come. You should lie down.
警察来了 我会叫你的
I'll wake you up when the police arrive.
你不认为我们疯了吗？
Do you think we're sick?
该死 当然不
Fuck, no.
老兄 你看其它那些
Dude, you look anywhere in the world…
没有法律的地方
where there's no law…
无论是在乍得还是新奥尔良
whether it's fucking Chad or New Orleans…
人们整天都他妈在做这种事
and this is the shit people are doing, bro.
我们是正常人
We're the normal ones.
你知道进去后要做什么吗？
Any idea what you're gonna do in there?
你不会想知道的
You don't even wanna know.
你决不想知道的
上帝
Jesus.
他们听着呢 他们听着呢
They're listening. They're listening.
贝思 是我 斯图亚特 我们在丰收节上见过的
Beth, it's me. It's Stuart. From the fair.
不要大声说话 好吗？
Don't talk loud. Okay?
如果他们听见我们这样说话
If they hear us talking like this…
他们会把我们都杀死的
they're gonna fucking kill us both.
你明白我的意思吗？
You hear me?
我需要知道你听见我说的了
I need to know you're listening.
好吗？
Okay?
你究竟要干什么？
What the fuck are you doing?
这是什么地方？我们现在他妈在哪？
What is this place? Where the fuck are we?
斯图亚特！
Stuart!
记着当时我说过
Remember when I said that…
我也不知道自己来这里干吗么？
I didn't know what I was doing here?
其实
Well…
这就是我来这里的目的
this is what I'm doing here.
这里是什么地方？
What is this place?
这里…
This place…
人们来这里…
People come here…
人们来这里杀人
People come here to kill people.
什么？谁杀人？
What? Who kills?
噢 天呐 他们要杀我们？
Oh, my God, are they gonna kill us?
其实
Well…
不是
not…
我们
us.
噢 上帝
Oh, my God.
你要杀我吗？
Oh, my God. Are you gonna kill me?
- 你要杀死我！- 不 不 不
- You're gonna kill me! - No, no! No, no.
不 上帝 不是的
No. Jesus, no. No.
那么你究竟在这里干吗？
Then what the fuck are you doing here?
你穿的什么衣服？
What the fuck are you wearing?
别人带我来这的
Someone brought me here…
和你一样
the same as you.
我认识的人
Someone I know.
听着
Look…
他想让我
he wanted me to…
和他一起干这个
To do this with him.
什么？
What?
斯图亚特 求你了
Stuart, please.
求你让我走
Please just let me go.
把我从椅子上放下来
Help me get out of this chair.
求你把我从椅子上放下来！
Please. Please help me get out of this chair.
把我放下来！
Get me out of this chair, please!
你以前能用这张漂亮脸蛋
You probably used that face…
得到你他妈想要的任何东西
to get whatever the fuck you wanted.
他妈的骚货
Fucking skank.
噢 这太他妈的有趣了
Oh, that's fucking rich.
你真该好好看看你现在那张脸
You should see your fucking face.
- 我们要离开这里 - 我们不能
- We gotta get out of here. - We can't.
他们认为你会杀死我吗？
They think you're gonna kill me?
你跟他们不一样 你不是禽兽
You're not some monster.
- 我不是那种人 - 我知道
- I'm not that guy. - No.
我知道的
No, I know.
- 我知道你是个好人 - 我不是那种人
- I know you're a good person. - I'm not that guy.
我知道 你当然不是
I know. Of course not.
我不是那种人
I'm not that guy.
- 好的 好的 - 我不是那种人
- Okay. Okay. - I'm not that guy.
我们要离开这里
We're gonna get out of here.
我不是那种人
I'm not that guy.
应该有一个密
There must be a co…
噢 该死 该死
Oh, fuck. Fuck.
上帝！见鬼！
Christ! Fuck!
天！
God!
该死！
Fuck!
你没有家庭吗？你没有妻子吗？
Don't you have family? Don't you have a wife?
我的妻子？
My wife?
我不能杀死我妻子
I'm not allowed to kill my wife.
- 结束了？- 是的 我结束了
- Finish? - Yeah, I'm finished, all right.
嘿 你还没完事呢
Hey, hey! You cannot done.
你得进去 干掉她
You go in room, finish.
你知道什么 我他妈的已经完成了
You know what? I am fucking done.
如果你不满意
If you don't like it,
你可以自己进去干掉她啊
you can go in and finish her yourself.
你只有干完了才能离开 合同上是这样规定的
You cannot leave unless you complete.It's contract.
我他妈的付钱了！
I fucking paid!
你们收了我的钱 好好留着吧！
You have my money and you can keep it!
我不会再回去了 我已经干完了！
I am not going back in that room! I'm done!
嘿 嘿！
Hey! Hey!
你好 现在有个特价优惠
Hello. Special offer.
她只有20分钟活头了
But she's only available for the next 20 minutes.
你想要她吗？
Do you want her?
我们会通知你的
We'll let you know.
怎么了？
Yes?
抱歉打搅你
Apologies for interrupting you,
我们现在有个特价优惠
but we have special available right now.
非常不错的价格
Very good price.
托德在哪？
Where's Todd?
你朋友自己的问题
Problem with friend.
我能暂时借一下这个吗？
May I borrow this for a moment, please?
你觉得怎么样？
What do you think?
我该要她吗？
Should I do it?
我的意思是 只需不到1000块就能得到她
I mean, I wouldn't pay more than a grand for her…
虽然是这个样子 但是
in this kind of shape, but…
我想说 瞧瞧
I mean, look at that.
她坚持不了多久了 对吧？
She's not gonna last that long, huh?
你应该看看她对我朋友做的好事！
You should see what she did to my friend.
我要了
I'll take her.
你朋友的一个纪念品
A souvenir from your friend.
发现我有什么不同了吗？
Notice anything different about me?
我敢打赌你发现了
I bet you fucking do.
他妈的婊子
Fucking bitch.
现在尊重我了吧
Fucking respect me now.
我他妈的不为你工作
I don't fucking work for you!
我再也不为你干活
I don't work all fucking day for you…
让你他妈的羞辱我了
to humiliate me.
说我是狗屎
To tell me I'm shit.
别惹我
Never fuck me.
看看你
Look at you.
什么？
What?
什么 你有话要说？
What, you got something to say?
是吗 婊子？
Do you? You do, bitch?
是吗 好 这样更好
Yeah? Oh, good. Well, it better be fucking good.
让我听听 你要说什么？
Let's fucking hear it. What?
我不是你妻子！
I'm not your wife.
我不是你妻子 斯图亚特 我不是你妻子
I'm not your wife, Stuart. I'm not your wife.
她不了解你
She doesn't understand you.
她不像我这样了解你
She doesn't understand you like I do.
- 我能看见你很强壮 - 我是很强壮
- And I see how you're strong. - I am strong.
- 我他妈就是大力士 - 我明白
- I am fucking Hercules! - I see.
我知道 我看到了 我看到了
I know. I know. I see it. I see it.
我昨晚看到了
I saw it last night.
我希望你能吻我
I was hoping you would kiss me.
我想你吻我
I wanted you to kiss me.
我一晚上都在想你
I thought about you all night.
他妈地躺在地上
Get on the fucking floor.
你害怕了吗？
Are you scared?
最好是这样
You fucking better be.
我害怕了
I am.
我喜欢这样
I like it.
看着我
Look at me.
婊子
Bitch.
你这个婊子
You fucking whore.
到椅子上来！
Get in the chair!
他妈的到椅子上来！
Get in the fucking chair!
混蛋！
Fucker!
密码是什么？
What's the code?
去你妈的！
Fuck you!
密码是什么？
What's the fucking code?
- 你的生日 - 什么？
- Your birthday. - What?
你的生日是哪一天？
What is your birthday?
12月12号
December 12th.
太他妈的恶心了
Oh, that is fucking sick.
什么密码！门没开！
What the fuck? It's not opening.
他妈的没有开！
It's not fucking opening!
哦 是的 没错
Oh, yes, it is.
快动手 她就站在你后面 快杀了她！
Do it! She's right up there behind you! Kill her!
该死的 快开枪！
Motherfucker! Shoot her!
杀了她！杀了她！
Kill her! Kill her!
别开枪 小心 看在上帝的份上！
Don't shoot! Be careful, for God's sakes!
她会剪的 别开枪！
She'll cut! She'll fucking cut! Don't shoot!
她会剪的！
Fucking she'll cut! She'll cut!
把沙夏叫来！
Get Sasha!
快去啊！我是这里的客户
You gotta do it! I'm the fucking customer here!
快点 该死
Do it, for fuck's sake.
噢 我的天！
Jesus fucking Christ. Oh, shit!
- 沙夏！- 叫他来！
- Sasha! - Get him!
- 等等 我要付钱离开这里 - 等等！
- Wait! I wanna buy my way out of here. - Wait!
你可买不起的！
You can't afford it.
别跟我说「你买不起」
Don't tell me what I can't afford.
这里没有什么我买不起的
There's nothing I can't afford.
我可以买卖这里的所有人
I could buy and sell everyone in this room.
你要给父母打电话要钱吗？
You going to call your parents for money?
不 混蛋 是我自己的钱
No, motherfucker, it's my money.
只要给我一台PDA
Just get me a PDA,
一个电汇帐户和一个收款人姓名
a SWIFT number and a recipient name.
我在瑞士的
I have accounts in Switzerland,
卢森堡银行和马恩岛银行 都有帐户
Luxembourg and the Isle of Man.
只要说你的价格 相信我 我有钱
Just name your fucking price! Trust me, I got it.
好吧
Okay.
我们来谈判
We negotiate.
- 这是在胡扯！- 这是生意
- This is bullshit! - This is business.
我会付更多钱！
I'll pay more!
不能用你的房屋二次抵押
Not with a second mortgage on your house…
和你女儿私立学校的学费吧
and your daughter's private-school tuition.
所以之前都是你朋友给你买的单
That's why your friend pay.
价钱多少？
What's the number?
钱并不是唯一的问题
Money is not the only issue.
我们这里按合同办事
We have contract here.
什么样的合同？
What kind of contract?
来这里的每一个人
Anyone who come to this place…
如果不杀人的话
cannot leave…
是不能离开的
without killing.
他们最后还会杀你的
They're still gonna kill you,
你这个愚蠢的臭婊子
you fucking stupid cunt.
你刚才说我什么？
What did you say to me?
你这个愚蠢的臭婊子！
You're a stupid fucking cu…!
让他失血而亡吧
Let him bleed to death.
米夏 别吃！
Misha, no!
这里很棒吧？
Isn't this great?
嘿 拿回来！
Hey, get back here!
站住！
Wait!
站住！站住！
Wait! Wait!
站住！
Wait!
Hey!
你这个混蛋！站住！
You fucking shit! Wait!